Let's get started with the lesson,
我们开始上课吧
regions and availability zones.
区域和可用性区域
Later, we'll get into service level resiliency,
稍后 我们将进入服务级别弹性
understanding business objectives, and reacting to failure.
了解业务目标 并对故障作出反应
In this lesson, you will learn about
在本课中 您将了解有关
the physical and networking infrastructure that AWS provides.
AWS 提供的物理和网络基础结构
You'll built infrastructure that uses many of the capabilities of AWSs global footprint.
您将构建使用许多 AWS 全球足迹功能的基础架构
You'll begin at the highest level with AWS regions.
您将从最高级的 AWS 区域开始
Then, we'll dive in and look at availability zones that live within regions.
然后 我们将潜入并查看区域内的可用性区域
You will learn to distinguish between resources and specific regions
您将学习区分资源和特定区域
versus the global AWS services which span all regions.
与跨所有区域的全球 AWS 服务相比
Within regions are VPCs which are your own personal networks within AWS.
在区域内  VPC 是您自己在 AWS 内的个人网络
You will explore AWS networking by creating a new VPC and modifying
您将通过创建新的 VPC 和修改来探索 AWS 网络
its network layout and access within the VPC private network.
其在 VPC 专用网络中的网络布局和接入